Privacy Policy

For California Consumers, please [click here](#california) for information on your rights under the California Consumer Protection Act to access and control the use your data.

1. **Why does collect data on consumers?**

collects consumer data for the following business and commercial purposes:

* Relevancy Purposes, to provide Users with the most relevant experiences on our Website that we think are likely to be of interest to you.

* Transactional Purposes, to contact Users with our offers and promotions.
* Technical Purposes to provide notices, updates, security alerts and support information.
* Customer Service Purposes, to communicate with you.
* Reporting Purposes, to share consumer data with third-party reporting services.
* **From whom does collect consumer data?**

collects consumer data from sources in the following categories:

* Direct from Consumer, information that you provide to us directly.

* Automatic Data Collection , collected automatically when you visit or register on our Website, such as internet protocol (IP) address, device ID, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and/or click-stream data, and through the use of "cookies", "pixel tags" and similar tracking technologies. For additional information on such tracking technologies, see Section 5 below.
* **What consumer data does collect?**

collects data about consumers in the following categories:

* Identifying Data, such as e-mail address.

* Technical Data, such as IP address, site traffic data and data on any websites that referred you to us.
* Engagement Data, such as the web pages you viewed and other interactions on our Website.
* **Does share consumer data with third parties?**

shares consumer data with third parties in the following categories:

* Marketing Partners, such as advertisers or app developers who wish to target and/or retarget our Users with relevant advertisements on other websites or magazine publishers and direct-to-consumer merchants who wish to communicate directly with our customers and Users through name rental or exchange.

* Acquisition Partners, such as publishers and other third parties who display ads on their websites.
* Service Providers, such as optimization and attribution partners, advertisers, product vendors and publishers.
* Media Intermediaries, such as buy-side advertising platforms, media vendors, brokers, agencies or other intermediaries.
* Aggregators, such as data management platforms, advertisers and publishers.
* Supporting Partners, such as marketing advisors, consultants and other third-party industry participants who work with us on a commercial basis or provide advice or services to us to support our business.
* Your email will only be shared with our preferred mailing partner for the purpose of sending third party promotional email communications.
* **What are Cookies and other tracking technologies?**

and its partners may use cookies or similar technologies to recognize User access privileges to , analyze trends, administer the website, track users’ movements around the website, add advertisements for goods or services we think may interest you, estimate our audience size, and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

A cookie is a small data file that a website can send to the browser on your computer when you link to that website. A cookie can hold information deposited in the file by a website, which can then be read by other sites. A cookie is not a computer program, it does not extract personal information about you or from your computer and it does not read data on your hard drive or instruct your computer to perform any function.

You may be able to use your browser to give you the option of accepting or rejecting a cookie whenever you visit a website. You may also be able to use your browser or other software to clear cookies from your browser any time you wish. However, deleting a website's cookie may mean that some features of our Website will not operate correct. Besides cookies, we may use web beacons, tracking pixels or similar tracking mechanisms to track your usage patterns on our Website. Like cookies, these small files do not store, record or share any personal information about you. We utilize third-party internet service providers to collect site traffic data using such tracking technologies that can be embedded in our Website. These service providers can then provide us with aggregate and anonymous usage data to allow us to improve our Website. This usage data cannot in be associated with any personal information we have about you.

* **Can I opt-out of receiving email from ?**

Yes. Receiving email from is always optional.

* **What about third-party websites?**

By clicking on hyperlinks or banner advertisements on our Website, you may be redirected to websites owned and operated by advertisers and other third parties. does not control such websites or their owners and operators, and such websites are not subject to this Privacy Policy. Any data submitted on or collected by such a third-party website will be governed by the privacy policy on that website. We recommend that Users check the privacy policies of such third-party websites to see how their consumer data will be collected, processed and shared.

* **What does do to keep their Website secure?**

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once it is received, including appropriate organizational, technological and physical safeguards commensurate with the sensitivity of the personal information in question. Although we believe that the measures, we take to safeguard your data are appropriate, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

* **Does collect information from Users outside of the United States?**

Our Website is not intended to be used by visitors residing outside of the United States.

* **Does collect personal information from children?**

Our Website is not intended for or directed to persons under the age of sixteen, and does not intend to collect personal information from individuals in this age group. If receives actual notice that a person under the age of sixteen has provided personal information to , will promptly (immediately, in the case of persons under the age of thirteen) remove such information from its files.

* **Your California Privacy Rights.**

As detailed in this Privacy Policy, use, collect, disclose and sell personal information about the consumers who respond to our offers. California consumers who wish to learn more about such practice and their rights under the California Consumer Protection Act, including the right to opt out of the sale of your data, by emailing ccpa@.

* **Further Questions?**

We welcome any questions or comments you may have regarding this Privacy Policy or the use of your data. To contact us, please contact us at contact@ or by writing to 3651 Lindell Road Suite D1137 Las Vegas, NV 89103.

**Important information for California residents**

This section applies only to California residents. It describes how we collect, use and share Personal Information of California residents in operating our business, and their rights with respect to that Personal Information. For purposes of this section, “Personal Information” has the meaning given in the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”) but does not include information exempted from the scope of the CCPA.

Your California privacy rights. As a California resident, you have the rights listed below. However, these rights are not absolute, and in certain cases we may decline your request as permitted by law.

* **Information**. You can request the following information about how we have collected and used your Personal Information during the past 12 months:

* The categories of Personal Information that we have collected.

* The categories of sources from which we collected Personal Information.
* The business or commercial purpose for collecting and/or selling Personal Information.
* The categories of third parties with whom we share Personal Information.
* Whether we have disclosed your Personal Information for a business purpose, and if so, the categories of Personal Information received by each category of third party recipient.
* Whether we’ve sold your Personal Information, and if so, the categories of Personal Information received by each category of third party recipient.
* **Access**. You can request a copy of the Personal Information that we have collected about you during the past 12 months.
* **Deletion**. You can ask us to delete the Personal Information that we have collected from you.
* **Opt-out of sales**. If we sell your Personal Information, you can opt-out. In addition, if you direct us not to sell your Personal Information, we will consider it a request pursuant to California’s “Shine the Light” law to stop sharing your personal information covered by that law with third parties for their direct marketing purposes.
* **Opt-in**. If we know that you are younger than 16 years old, we will ask for your permission (or if you are younger than 13 years old, your parent’s or guardian’s permission) to sell your Personal Information before we do so.
* Nondiscrimination. You are entitled to exercise the rights described above free from discrimination in the form of legally prohibited increases in the price or decreases in the quality of our Service.

**How to exercise your rights**

You may exercise your California privacy rights described above as follows:

Right to information, access and deletion. You can request to exercise your information, access and deletion rights by visiting /ccpa. We are not responsible for notices that are not labeled or sent properly, or do not have complete information.

**Right to opt-out of the “sale” of your Personal Information**. Like many companies, we use services that help deliver interest-based ads to you. Our use of some of these services may be classified under California law as a “sale” of your Personal Information to the companies that provide the services because they collect information from our users (e.g., device data and online activity data) to help them serve ads more likely to interest you. You can request to opt-out out of this “sale” of your personal information here: /ccpa.

We reserve the right to confirm your California residence to process your requests and will need to confirm your identity to process your requests to exercise your information, access or deletion rights. As part of this process, government identification may be required. Consistent with California law, you may designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf. In order to designate an authorized agent to make a request on your behalf, you must provide a valid power of attorney, the requester’s valid government-issued identification, and the authorized agent’s valid government issued identification. We cannot process your request if you do not provide us with sufficient detail to allow us to understand and respond to it.

Disclosure or Sale of Personal Information. has not disclosed or sold Personal Information about California Consumers to third parties for business and commercial purposes in the last 12 months. does not knowingly collect or sell the Personal Information of persons under 16 years of age. The table below lists, for each category of Personal Information collected, the (i) categories of sources from which it was collected, (ii) the business or commercial purposes for which it was collected, and (iii) the categories of third parties with whom it was shared. In the table below, categories of consumer data, and categories of source, purpose and third-party sharing, are as described in the Privacy Policy.

|     |     |     |
| --- | --- | --- |
| **Categories** | **Examples** | **Collected** |
| A. Identifiers. | A real name, alias, postal address, unique personal identifier, online identifier, Internet Protocol address, email address, account name, Social Security number, driver’s license number, passport number, or other similar identifiers. | Yes |
| B. Personal information categories listed in the California Customer Records statute (Cal. Civ. Code § 1798.80(e)). | A name, signature, Social Security number, physical characteristics or description, address, telephone number, passport number, driver’s license or state identification card number, insurance policy number, education, employment, employment history, bank account number, credit card number, debit card number, or any other financial information, medical information, or health insurance information. Some personal information included in this category may overlap with other categories. | Yes |
| C. Protected classification characteristics under California or federal law. | Age (40 years or older), race, color, ancestry, national origin, citizenship, religion or creed, marital status, medical condition, physical or mental disability, sex (including gender, gender identity, gender expression, pregnancy or childbirth and related medical conditions), sexual orientation, veteran or military status, genetic information (including familial genetic information). | No  |
| D. Commercial information. | Records of personal property, products or services purchased, obtained, or considered, or other purchasing or consuming histories or tendencies. | No  |
| E. Biometric information. | Genetic, physiological, behavioral, and biological characteristics, or activity patterns used to extract a template or other identifier or identifying information, such as, fingerprints, faceprints, and voiceprints, iris or retina scans, keystroke, gait, or other physical patterns, and sleep, health, or exercise data. | No  |
| F. Internet or other similar network activity. | Browsing history, search history, information on a consumer’s interaction with a website, application, or advertisement. | Yes |
| G. Geolocation data. | Physical location or movements. | No  |
| H. Sensory data. | Audio, electronic, visual, thermal, olfactory, or similar information. | No  |
| I. Professional or employment-related information. | Current or past job history or performance evaluations. | No  |
| J. Non-public education information (per the Family Educational Rights and Privacy Act (20 U.S.C. Section 1232g, 34 C.F.R. Part 99)). | Education records directly related to a student maintained by an educational institution or party acting on its behalf, such as grades, transcripts, class lists, student schedules, student identification codes, student financial information, or student disciplinary records. | No  |
| K. Inferences drawn from other personal information. | Profile reflecting a person’s preferences, characteristics, psychological trends, predispositions, behavior, attitudes, intelligence, abilities, and aptitudes. | No  |

For questions or more information about your rights under the CCPA and this Statement of Consumer Privacy Rights, please contact ccpa@ or by writing to 3651 Lindell Road Suite D1137 Las Vegas, NV 89103.

Privacy Policy Last Updated: February 17, 2020

This promotion is in no way sponsored, endorsed or administered by, or associated with Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Snapchat, Youtube, Pinterest, LinkedIn or Google. You understand that you are providing your information to the owner of this sweepstakes and not to Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, Snapchat, Youtube, Pinterest, LinkedIn or Google.

© 2022 SweepStacks.com - All Rights Reserved  
Click here to unsubscribe from our mailing list
